Saidnabi Yuldashkhadjaev

.NET Developer



♥ Tashkent. Uzbekistan

PROFILE

I have been actively involved in Information Technology for 1 years, specializing in web app development with excellent knowledge of software development methodologies, frameworks, and Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC). I have experience in developing applications for various industries including Healthcare, Finance, and Educational sectors.I possess strong communication skills and the ability to interact professionally with diverse groups.

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS Self-Study, Communication, Problem-Solving, Time

management, Attention todetail, Teamwork, Continuous

learning, Critical thinking, Networking, Creativity

HARD SKILLS C#, ASP.NET Core Web API, ASP.NET Core MVC, Entity

Framework Core, MS SQL Server, PostgreSQL, LINQ, REST, GraphQL, Unit Testing, Design Principles and Patterns.

EDUCATION

Kimyo International University in Tashkent

September 2019 - May 2023

Najot Ta'lim

July 2022 - June 2023

Information System Engineering

University experience built my programming foundation, teaching essential skills for software development career.

.NET Backend

I gained skills in C# programming, ASP.NET web development, database management, OOP principles, and hands-on project implementation.

Mohirdey

November 2022 - May 2023

.NET Backend

In my self-study of the .NET online course, I covered advanced topics including C# programming, MVC, LINQ, asynchronous programming, security, and database management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Food - Market

2019 - 2021

Sales Manager

Product sales, marketing

Sareed LTD

2023 - Now

.NET Developer

Software applications development

ACTIVITIES

Sharpist - 2022

2022 - December

Volunteer

Microsoft Developers Community in Uzbekistan

PROJECTS

FleetFlow

Team project

Description - Best delivering system

Role - .NET developer in the FleetFlow project, I was actively involved in the development and implementation of key features and functionalities.

Technologies Used - .NET Framework, C#, ASP.NET Core, ASP.NET Core Web API, Entity Framework, REST, GraphQL, LINQ, Unit Testing

Key Accomplishments -

Recognizing the need for a more organized and scalable architecture, I successfully reengineered the project's API and service layers. Implemented the Service Layer, resulting in a substantial transformation with approximately 80% of the project's structure modified.

Transferred the core business logic to the Service Layer, which accounted for approximately 70% of the overall codebase. The most important thing is that I separated the services from the API layer. This means that the API layer is focused on handling requests and responses, while the Service layer takes care of the business logic, such as processing data and performing operations

Website - fleetflow.uz

Ahsan

Team project - (Build processing)

Ahsan is a project management tool similar to Trello and Jira. It allows you to create boards, lists, and cards to track tasks and collaborate with team members.

Ubee

Team Project - (Build processing)

Ubee application is a digital wallet that allows users to store, manage, and make transactions with their digital assets, such as cryptocurrencies, loyalty points, and gift cards. These applications often provide users with a user-friendly interface to manage their digital assets and enable quick and easy transactions.

LANGUAGES

Uzbek - Native/Bilingual English - Limited Working Proficiency Russian - Elementary